Country Name	Country Code	Region	IncomeGroup	SpecialNotes
Aruba	ABW	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	SNA data for 2000-2011 are updated from official government statistics; 1994-1999 from UN databases. Base year has changed from 1995 to 2000.
Afghanistan	AFG	South Asia	Low income	Fiscal year end: March 20; reporting period for national accounts data: FY (from 2013 are CY). National accounts data are sourced from the IMF and differ from the Central Statistics Organization numbers due to exclusion of the opium economy.
Angola	AGO	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income	"April 2013 database update: Based on IMF data, national accounts data were revised for 2000 onward; the base year changed to 2002."
Albania	ALB	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	
Andorra	AND	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	
Arab World	ARB			Arab World aggregate. Arab World is composed of members of the League of Arab States.
United Arab Emirates	ARE	Middle East & North Africa	High income: nonOECD	"April 2013 database update: Based on data from the National Bureau of Statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2001 onward; the base year changed to 2007."
Argentina	ARG	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	The base year has changed to 2004.
Armenia	ARM	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income	
American Samoa	ASM	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	
Antigua and Barbuda	ATG	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	"April 2012 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2000 onward; the base year changed to 2006."
Australia	AUS	East Asia & Pacific	High income: OECD	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. Value added current series updated by the Australian Bureau of Statistics; data revised from 1990 onward; Australia reports using SNA 2008.
Austria	AUT	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 13.7603 Austrian schilling. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Azerbaijan	AZE	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	April 2012 database update: National accounts historical expenditure series in constant prices were revised in line with State Statistical Committee data that were not previously available.
Burundi	BDI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	
Belgium	BEL	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 40.3399 Belgian franc. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Benin	BEN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	
Burkina Faso	BFA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	
Bangladesh	BGD	South Asia	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. The new base year is 2005/06.
Bulgaria	BGR	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	The new reference year for chain linked series is 2010. April 2011 database update: The National Statistical Office revised national accounts data from 1995 onward. GDP in current prices were about 4 percent higher than previous estimates.
Bahrain	BHR	Middle East & North Africa	High income: nonOECD	Based on official government statistics; the new base year is 2010.
"Bahamas, The"	BHS	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Bosnia and Herzegovina	BIH	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	Based on official government statistics for chain linked series; the new reference year is 2010.
Belarus	BLR	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	
Belize	BLZ	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	
Bermuda	BMU	North America	High income: nonOECD	
Bolivia	BOL	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	
Brazil	BRA	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	
Barbados	BRB	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Brunei Darussalam	BRN	East Asia & Pacific	High income: nonOECD	
Bhutan	BTN	South Asia	Lower middle income	April 2013 database update: Data were updated using the government of Bhutan macroeconomic framework.
Botswana	BWA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income	"Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Based on official government statistics, national accounts data have been revised from 2006 onward; the new base year is 2006. Data before 2006 were reported on a fiscal year basis."
Central African Republic	CAF	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	
Canada	CAN	North America	High income: OECD	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.
Central Europe and the Baltics	CEB			Central Europe and the Baltics aggregate.
Switzerland	CHE	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	
Channel Islands	CHI	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	
Chile	CHL	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: OECD	
China	CHN	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	"On 1 July 1997 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Hong Kong; and on 20 December 1999 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Macao. Unless otherwise noted, data for China do not include data for Hong Kong SAR, China; Macao SAR, China; or Taiwan, China. Based on data from the National Bureau of Statistics, the methodology for national accounts exports and imports of goods and services in constant prices have been revised from 2000 onward."
Côte d'Ivoire	CIV	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	The new base year is 2009.
Cameroon	CMR	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	
"Congo, Dem. Rep."	COD	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	Based on official government statistics; the new base year 2005.
"Congo, Rep."	COG	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"April 2013 database update: Based on IMF data, national accounts data were revised for 1990 onward; the base year changed to 1990."
Colombia	COL	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	
Comoros	COM	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	
Cabo Verde	CPV	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"Cabo Verde is the new name for the country previously listed as Cape Verde. Based on official government statistics and IMF data, national accounts data have been revised from 1990 onward; the new base year is 2007."
Costa Rica	CRI	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	
Caribbean small states	CSS			"Caribbean small states aggregate. Includes Antigua and Barbuda, The Bahamas, Barbados, Belize, Guyana, Suriname, Dominica, Grenada, Jamaica, St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Lucia, St. Vincent and the Grenadines, and Trinidad and Tobago."
Cuba	CUB	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	
Curaçao	CUW	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Cayman Islands	CYM	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Cyprus	CYP	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2008: 1 euro = 0.585274 Cyprus pounds. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Czech Republic	CZE	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	
Germany	DEU	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 1.95583 German mark. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Djibouti	DJI	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income	
Dominica	DMA	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"April 2012 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2000 onward; the base year changed to 2006."
Denmark	DNK	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	
Dominican Republic	DOM	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	
Algeria	DZA	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income	
East Asia & Pacific	EAP			East Asia and Pacific regional aggregate (does not include high-income economies).
East Asia & Pacific (all income levels)	EAS			East Asia and Pacific regional aggregate (including high-income economies).
Europe & Central Asia	ECA			Europe and Central Asia regional aggregate (does not include high-income economies).
Europe & Central Asia (all income levels)	ECS			Europe and Central Asia regional aggregate (including high-income economies).
Ecuador	ECU	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	National accounts have been revised from 1965 onward based on official government data; the new base year is 2007. The large upward changes are due to an improved calculation method for nominal GDP.
"Egypt, Arab Rep."	EGY	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. The new base year is 2001/02.
Euro area	EMU			Euro area aggregate.
Eritrea	ERI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"April 2013 database update: Based on IMF data, national accounts data were revised for 2000 onward; the base year changed to 2000."
Spain	ESP	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 166.386 Spanish peseta. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Estonia	EST	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2011: 1 euro = 15.6466 Estonian kroon. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Ethiopia	ETH	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"Fiscal year end: July 7; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. Based on IMF data, national accounts data have been revised for 2000 onward; the new base year is 2010/11."
European Union	EUU			European Union aggregate.
Fragile and conflict affected situations	FCS			"Fragile situations aggregate. Note:  Countries with fragile situations are primarily International Development Association-eligible countries and nonmember or inactive countries and territories with a 3.2 or lower harmonized average of the World Bank's Country Policy and Institutional Assessment rating and the corresponding rating by a regional development bank, or that have had a UN or regional peacebuilding and political mission (for example by the African Union, European Union, or Organization of American States) or peacekeeping mission (for example, by the African Union, European Union, North Atlantic Treaty Organization, or Organization of American States) during the last three years.  This definition is pursuant to an agreement between the World Bank and other multilateral development banks at the start of the International Development Association 15 round in 2007. The list of countries and territories with fragile situations  is imperfect and used here to reflect a complex concept. The World Bank continues to work with partners and client countries to refine the concept."
Finland	FIN	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 5.94573 Finnish markka. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Fiji	FJI	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	"Based on data from the Bureau of Statistics, national accounts data on the expenditure side have been revised from 2005 onward; the new base year is 2005."
France	FRA	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 6.55957 French franc. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Faeroe Islands	FRO	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	
"Micronesia, Fed. Sts."	FSM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"Fiscal year ends on September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. Based on the Pacific and Virgin Islands Training Initiative, national accounts data have been revised from 2009 onward. 2013 estimates are based on the IMF Small States Monitor, Issue 1.2014. In 2010, the government statistical office revised national accounts data for 1995-2008."
Gabon	GAB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income	Based on IMF data and official government statistics; the new base year is 2001.
United Kingdom	GBR	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	
Georgia	GEO	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income	
Ghana	GHA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"In 2010, the Ghana Statistical Service revised the base year for Ghana's national accounts series from 1993 to 2006. The new GDP data were about 60 percent higher than previously reported and incorporated improved data sources and methodology."
Guinea	GIN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	
"Gambia, The"	GMB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. April 2013 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2004 onward; the base year changed to 2004."
Guinea-Bissau	GNB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"In 2010, national accounts data for 2003-09 were revised. The new data had broader coverage of all sectors of the economy, and GDP in current prices averaged 89 percent higher than previous estimates."
Equatorial Guinea	GNQ	Sub-Saharan Africa	High income: nonOECD	National accounts have been revised from 1980 onward based on IMF data and official government statistics; the new base year is 2006.
Greece	GRC	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 340.75 Greek drachma. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Grenada	GRD	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"April 2012 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2000 onward; the base year changed to 2006."
Greenland	GRL	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	
Guatemala	GTM	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	
Guam	GUM	East Asia & Pacific	High income: nonOECD	
Guyana	GUY	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	"In 2010, the Bureau of Statistics introduced a new series of GDP rebased to year 2006. Current price GDP averaged 63 percent higher than previous estimates."
High income	HIC			"High income group aggregate. High-income economies are those in which 2014 GNI per capita was $12,736 or more."
"Hong Kong SAR, China"	HKG	East Asia & Pacific	High income: nonOECD	"On 1 July 1997 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Hong Kong. Unless otherwise noted, data for China do not include data for Hong Kong SAR, China; Macao SAR, China; or Taiwan, China. Agriculture value added includes mining and quarrying."
Honduras	HND	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	
Heavily indebted poor countries (HIPC)	HPC			Heavily indebted poor countries aggregate.
Croatia	HRV	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	"The new reference year for chain linked series is 2010. April 2013 database update: Based on official government statistics, the base year for constant price series changed to 2005."
Haiti	HTI	Latin America & Caribbean	Low income	"Fiscal year end: September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. In 2010, the government revised national accounts data following changes in the methodology. Current price series since 1991 and constant price series since 1996 were revised."
Hungary	HUN	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"April 2012 database update: Based on data from the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development, national accounts data were revised for 1991 onward."
Indonesia	IDN	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Data for Indonesia include Timor-Leste through 1999 unless otherwise noted. New base year is 2010.
Isle of Man	IMN	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	
India	IND	South Asia	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. Based on official government statistics; the new base year is 2011/12. India reports using SNA 2008.
Ireland	IRL	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 0.787564 Irish pound. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
"Iran, Islamic Rep."	IRN	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: March 20; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.
Iraq	IRQ	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income	
Iceland	ISL	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	
Israel	ISR	Middle East & North Africa	High income: OECD	Based on official government statistics for chain linked series; the new reference year is 2010.
Italy	ITA	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 1936.27 Italian lira. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Jamaica	JAM	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"April 2013 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2002 onward; the base year changed to 2007."
Jordan	JOR	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income	
Japan	JPN	East Asia & Pacific	High income: OECD	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.
Kazakhstan	KAZ	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	The new reference year for chain linked series is 2005.
Kenya	KEN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Based on official government statistics; the new base year is 2009.
Kyrgyz Republic	KGZ	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income	
Cambodia	KHM	East Asia & Pacific	Low income	
Kiribati	KIR	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"Based on IMF and World Bank data, GDP in current and constant prices have been revised from 2000 onward. Value added components are calculated using shares from the Asian Development Bank."
St. Kitts and Nevis	KNA	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	"April 2012 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2000 onward; the base year changed to 2006."
"Korea, Rep."	KOR	East Asia & Pacific	High income: OECD	The new base year is 2010. GDP data are available from 1970 onward while components are revised from 2000 onward only. Historical data in constant prices are linked to preserve growth rates.
Kosovo	KSV	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income	"Kosovo became a World Bank member on June 29, 2009. Since 1999, Kosovo has been a territory under international administration pursuant to UN Security Council Resolution 1244 (1999)."
Kuwait	KWT	Middle East & North Africa	High income: nonOECD	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Based on official government statistics; the new base year is 2010.
Latin America & Caribbean	LAC			Latin America and Caribbean regional aggregate (does not include high-income economies).
Lao PDR	LAO	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	
Lebanon	LBN	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income	
Liberia	LBR	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	National accounts local currency data have been revised to be reported in U.S. dollars.
Libya	LBY	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income	National accounts data are revised from 2010 to 2013 based on IMF and World Bank staff estimates.
St. Lucia	LCA	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"April 2012 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2000 onward; the base year changed to 2006."
Latin America & Caribbean (all income levels)	LCN			Latin America and Caribbean regional aggregate (including high-income economies).
Least developed countries: UN classification	LDC			Least developed countries (UN classification) aggregate.
Low income	LIC			"Low income group aggregate. Low-income economies are those in which 2014 GNI per capita was $1,045 or less."
Liechtenstein	LIE	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	
Sri Lanka	LKA	South Asia	Lower middle income	
Lower middle income	LMC			"Lower middle income group aggregate. Lower-middle-income economies are those in which 2014 GNI per capita was between $1,046 and $4,125."
Low & middle income	LMY			"Low and middle income group aggregate (all developing economies). Low- and middle-income economies are those in which 2014 GNI per capita was $12,735 or less."
Lesotho	LSO	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.
Lithuania	LTU	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2015: 1 euro = 3.45280 Lithuanian litas. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Luxembourg	LUX	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 40.3399 Luxembourg franc. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Latvia	LVA	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2014: 1 euro = 0.702804 Latvian lats. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
"Macao SAR, China"	MAC	East Asia & Pacific	High income: nonOECD	"On 20 December 1999 China resumed its exercise of sovereignty over Macao. Unless otherwise noted, data for China do not include data for Hong Kong SAR, China; Macao SAR, China; or Taiwan, China."
St. Martin (French part)	MAF	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Morocco	MAR	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income	
Monaco	MCO	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	
Moldova	MDA	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income	
Madagascar	MDG	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	
Maldives	MDV	South Asia	Upper middle income	April 2012 database update: The Department of National Planning revised national accounts data for 2000 onward; the base year changed to 2003.
Middle East & North Africa (all income levels)	MEA			Middle East and North Africa regional aggregate (including high-income economies).
Mexico	MEX	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	The new base year is 2008.
Marshall Islands	MHL	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	Fiscal year ends on September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.
Middle income	MIC			"Middle income group aggregate. Middle-income economies are those in which 2014 GNI per capita was between $1,046 and $12,735."
"Macedonia, FYR"	MKD	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	New base year is 2005.
Mali	MLI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	
Malta	MLT	Middle East & North Africa	High income: nonOECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2008: 1 euro = 0.4293 Maltese lira. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Myanmar	MMR	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.
Middle East & North Africa	MNA			Middle East and North Africa regional aggregate (does not include high-income economies).
Montenegro	MNE	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Montenegro declared independence from Serbia and Montenegro on June 3, 2006. Where available, data for each country are shown separately. However, for Serbia, some indicators continue to include data for Montenegro through 2005."
Mongolia	MNG	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	The new base year is 2010.
Northern Mariana Islands	MNP	East Asia & Pacific	High income: nonOECD	
Mozambique	MOZ	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	Based on official government statistics; the new base year is 2009.
Mauritania	MRT	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Based on official statistics from the Ministry of Economic Affairs and Development; the base year has been returned to 2004.
Mauritius	MUS	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income	
Malawi	MWI	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Based on IMF data, national accounts data have been revised for 2000 onward; the new base year is 2009."
Malaysia	MYS	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	
North America	NAC			North America regional aggregate. There are no economies in North America classified as low or middle income.
Namibia	NAM	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income	"Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Based on official government statistics, national accounts data have been revised from 1980 onward; the new base year is 2010."
New Caledonia	NCL	East Asia & Pacific	High income: nonOECD	
Niger	NER	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"Based on official government statistics, national accounts data have been revised from 2006 onward; the new base year is 2006."
Nigeria	NGA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"Based on official government statistics released 6 April, 2014, national accounts data have been revised from 2010 onward; the new base year is 2010. The new GDP data are 60 to 75 percent higher than previously reported and incorporate improved data sources and methodology. Nigeria reports using SNA 2008."
Nicaragua	NIC	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	"April 2013 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 1994 onward; the base year changed to 2006."
Netherlands	NLD	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 2.20371 Netherlands guilder. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
High income: nonOECD	NOC			"High income nonOECD aggregate. High-income economies are those in which 2014 GNI per capita was $12,736 or more."
Norway	NOR	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	
Nepal	NPL	South Asia	Low income	Fiscal year end: July 14; reporting period for national accounts data: FY.
New Zealand	NZL	East Asia & Pacific	High income: OECD	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.
High income: OECD	OEC			"High income OECD members aggregate. High-income economies are those in which 2014 GNI per capita was $12,736 or more."
OECD members	OED			"OECD members aggregate (all, including developing countries)."
Oman	OMN	Middle East & North Africa	High income: nonOECD	Based on official government statistics; the new base year is 2010.
Other small states	OSS			"Other small states aggregate. Includes Bhutan, Botswana, Cabo Verde, Comoros, Djibouti, Equatorial Guinea, Gabon, The Gambia, Guinea-Bissau, Lesotho, Maldives, Mauritius, Montenegro, Namibia, Sao Tome and Principe, Seychelles, Swaziland, and Timor-Leste."
Pakistan	PAK	South Asia	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. The new base year is 2005/06.
Panama	PAN	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	The new base year is 2007.
Peru	PER	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	The new base year is 2007.
Philippines	PHL	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"Source for GNI and net income from abroad is changed to national statistical office from central bank. April 2012 database update: National accounts data were revised for 1998 onward. Because intellectual property products are now reported as a part of gross fixed capital formation, gross domestic product (GDP) in current prices averaged 4 percent higher than previous estimates."
Palau	PLW	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	Fiscal year ends on September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. National accounts data are revised based on IMF reports.
Papua New Guinea	PNG	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	
Poland	POL	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	
Puerto Rico	PRI	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	"Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. April 2012 database update: Based on data from the Instituto de Estadísticas de Puerto Rico, national accounts data were revised for 2001 onward."
"Korea, Dem. Rep."	PRK	East Asia & Pacific	Low income	
Portugal	PRT	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate was adopted by the EU Council on January 1, 1999: 1 euro = 200.482 Portuguese escudo. Please note that historical data before 1999 are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Paraguay	PRY	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"National accounts data have been revised from 1960 onward. The methodology and base year have not changed but the output of two hydroelectric plants (shared with neighboring countries) has been added raising GDP from previous estimates. On the supply side, it was added in ""gas, electricity and water."" On the demand side changes were mainly to exports, but also for imports, investment and consumption. National accounts price valuations for 1991 to 2012 have also been corrected and changed from VAP to VAB."
West Bank and Gaza	PSE	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income	The new base year is 2004.
Pacific island small states	PSS			"Pacific island small states aggregate. Includes Fiji, Kiribati, Marshall Islands, Federated States of Micronesia, Palau, Samoa, Solomon Islands, Tonga, Tuvalu, and Vanuatu."
French Polynesia	PYF	East Asia & Pacific	High income: nonOECD	
Qatar	QAT	Middle East & North Africa	High income: nonOECD	
Romania	ROU	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	
Russian Federation	RUS	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	
Rwanda	RWA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"Based on official government statistics, national accounts data are revised for 2006 onward; the new base year is 2011. Rwanda reports using SNA 2008."
South Asia	SAS			South Asia regional aggregate. There are no economies in South Asia classified as high income.
Saudi Arabia	SAU	Middle East & North Africa	High income: nonOECD	The new base year is 2010.
Sudan	SDN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"Demographic data (total population, life expectancy, fertility, child mortality, migration), education series, and HIV prevalence are reported separately for Sudan and South Sudan; see specific notes for other series. National accounts data exclude South Sudan after July 9, 2011. Other data reported for Sudan generally include South Sudan to 2011 unless otherwise noted. External debt data and land-related data (including population density, but excluding surface area after 2010) for all years include South Sudan."
Senegal	SEN	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	
Singapore	SGP	East Asia & Pacific	High income: nonOECD	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. Country reports using a blend of SNA 1993 and SNA 2008. April 2012 database update: National accounts time series were replaced with official government statistics.
Solomon Islands	SLB	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	National accounts data have been revised from 2007 to 2013 based on IMF reports.
Sierra Leone	SLE	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. April 2013 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 1990 onward; the base year changed to 2006."
El Salvador	SLV	Latin America & Caribbean	Lower middle income	
San Marino	SMR	Europe & Central Asia	High income: nonOECD	
Somalia	SOM	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	
Serbia	SRB	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"Montenegro declared independence from Serbia and Montenegro on June 3, 2006. Where available, data for each country are shown separately. However, for Serbia, some indicators, such as those series for which data appear only for Serbia and not Montenegro--e.g., aid, environment, external debt, balance of payments, various social indicators excluding population--continue to include data for Montenegro through 2005. Moreover, data from 1999 onward for Serbia for most indicators exclude data for Kosovo, 1999 being the year when Kosovo became a territory under international administration pursuant to UN Security Council Resolution 1244 (1999); any exceptions are noted. Kosovo became a World Bank member on June 29, 2009; available data are shown separately for Kosovo. In 2011, the Statistical Office of Serbia improved the methodology of national accounts data for 2003 onward. Specifically, the classification of sectors was revised. The new reference year for chain linked series is 2010."
Sub-Saharan Africa	SSA			Sub-Saharan Africa regional aggregate (does not include high-income economies).
South Sudan	SSD	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"South Sudan declared its independence on July 9, 2011. Data are shown separately for South Sudan where available."
Sub-Saharan Africa (all income levels)	SSF			Sub-Saharan Africa regional aggregate (including high-income economies).
Small states	SST			"Small states aggregate. Includes 41 members of the Small States Forum. (Does not include the high-income countries Bahrain, Brunei Darussalam, Cyprus, Estonia, Iceland, Malta, Qatar, and San Marino.)"
São Tomé and Principe	STP	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	
Suriname	SUR	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	
Slovak Republic	SVK	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2009: 1 euro = 30.126 Slovak koruna. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Slovenia	SVN	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	"A simple multiplier is used to convert the national currencies of EMU members to euros. The following irrevocable euro conversion rate entered into force on January 1, 2007: 1 euro = 239.64 Slovenian tolar. Please note that historical data are not actual euros and are not comparable or suitable for aggregation across countries."
Sweden	SWE	Europe & Central Asia	High income: OECD	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.
Swaziland	SWZ	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.
Sint Maarten (Dutch part)	SXM	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Seychelles	SYC	Sub-Saharan Africa	High income: nonOECD	"April 2013 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 1976 onward; the base year changed to 2006."
Syrian Arab Republic	SYR	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income	"April 2013 database update: Based on data from the Central Bureau of Statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2003 onward."
Turks and Caicos Islands	TCA	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Chad	TCD	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"Based on IMF data, national accounts data have been revised for 2005 onward; the new base year is 2005."
Togo	TGO	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"April 2013 database update: Based on IMF data, national accounts data have been revised for 2000; the new base year is 2000."
Thailand	THA	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.
Tajikistan	TJK	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income	
Turkmenistan	TKM	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	"On January 1, 2009, the Turkmen manat was redenominated (1 new manat = 5,000 old manats)."
Timor-Leste	TLS	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"Based on official government statistics, national account data have been revised, and value added is measured at basic prices; the new base year is 2010."
Tonga	TON	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	"2013 national accounts estimates are based on IMF reports. Fiscal year ends on June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. April 2013 database update: Based on data from the National Bureau of Statistics, national accounts data were revised; the base year changed to 2010/11."
Trinidad and Tobago	TTO	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Tunisia	TUN	Middle East & North Africa	Upper middle income	
Turkey	TUR	Europe & Central Asia	Upper middle income	
Tuvalu	TUV	East Asia & Pacific	Upper middle income	2013 national accounts estimates are based on IMF reports. Value added is measured at producer prices up to 1999 and at basic prices from 2000 onward.
Tanzania	TZA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	The new base year is 2007. Tanzania reports using a blend of SNA 1993 and SNA 2008.
Uganda	UGA	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. Based on official government statistics; the new base year is 2009/10. Uganda reports using SNA 2008. Price valuation is in producer prices.
Ukraine	UKR	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income	
Upper middle income	UMC			"Upper middle income group aggregate. Upper-middle-income economies are those in which 2014 GNI per capita was between $4,126 and $12,735."
Uruguay	URY	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	"In 2011, the Central Bank revised national accounts data for 2006 onward."
United States	USA	North America	High income: OECD	Fiscal year end: September 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY.
Uzbekistan	UZB	Europe & Central Asia	Lower middle income	
St. Vincent and the Grenadines	VCT	Latin America & Caribbean	Upper middle income	"April 2012 database update: Based on official government statistics, national accounts data were revised for 2000 onward; the base year changed to 2006."
"Venezuela, RB"	VEN	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Virgin Islands (U.S.)	VIR	Latin America & Caribbean	High income: nonOECD	
Vietnam	VNM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"Based on data from the Vietnam Statistics Office, national accounts data have been revised from 2000 onward; the new base year is 2010."
Vanuatu	VUT	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"2013 national accounts estimates are based on IMF reports. Based on official government statistics, value added is measured at producer prices through 1997 and at basic prices from 1998 onward."
World	WLD			World aggregate.
Samoa	WSM	East Asia & Pacific	Lower middle income	"Fiscal year ends on June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: FY. Data are revised from Samoa Bureau of Statistics and Central Bank of Samoa. The new base year is 2008/09. Other methodological changes include increased reliance on summary data from the country’s Value Added Goods and Services Tax system, incorporation of more recent benchmarks, and use of improved data sources."
"Yemen, Rep."	YEM	Middle East & North Africa	Lower middle income	"Based on official government statistics and International Monetary Fund data, national accounts data have been revised for 1990 onward. The new base year is 2007."
South Africa	ZAF	Sub-Saharan Africa	Upper middle income	Fiscal year end: March 31; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. The new base year is 2010. South Africa reports using SNA 2008.
Zambia	ZMB	Sub-Saharan Africa	Lower middle income	"The new base year is 2010. National accounts data were rebased to reflect the January 1, 2013, introduction of the new Zambian kwacha at a rate of 1,000 old kwacha = 1 new kwacha. Zambia reports using SNA 2008."
Zimbabwe	ZWE	Sub-Saharan Africa	Low income	"Fiscal year end: June 30; reporting period for national accounts data: CY. As of January 2009, multiple hard currencies, such as rand, pound sterling, euro and U.S. dollar are in use. Data are reported in U.S. dollars, the most-used currency."